luxembourgwebservices.com 2018-07-15

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                                    PRIVACY POLICY
   This document is the proprietary and exclusive property of LuxNetwork S.A. S.A. except as otherwise indicated. No part of this document,
   in whole or in part, may be reproduced, stored, transmitted, or used for design purposes without the prior written permission of LuxNetwork
   S.A. S.A.
Company Confidential – Privacy Policy                       Version 1.0                                                                page 1|3

Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and this Privacy Policy of LuxNetwork S.A.. sets out what
information we collect and how we use it.
Information We may collect from You
We may collect and process the following data about you:
                        §§ information that you provide when you use our website luxembourgwebservices.com (“Our Site”).
                             This includes information provided at the time of registering for our services. We may also ask you for
                             information when you report a problem or share a suggestion with our services on Our Site;
                        §§ if you contact us telephone or in writing, we may keep a record of that correspondence or
                             communication;
                        §§ details of transactions you carry out through Our Site and of the fulfillment of your orders; and
                        §§ details of your visits to Our Site and the resources that you access.
If you have provided us with the personal data of another person, you confirm that he/she consents to the processing of his/her
personal data and that you have informed him/her of our identity as a Data Controller and provide him/her with a copy of this
Privacy Policy.
IP addresses & cookies
When you visit our website, we collect the web page you came from, your browser’s user agent string, any keywords you used
in a search engine, your computer’s IP address, the time and date, the name of the pages your computer visited, and how long
it spent on each page. We send to your computer one or more cookies a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely
identify your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends.
Use of the information collected
We use information held about you in the following ways:
                        §§   to ensure that content from Our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your
                             computer;
                        §§   to provide you with information, products and/or services that you request from us or which we
                             feel may interest you;
                        §§   to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us; and
                        §§   to notify you about changes to our products.
We may contact you by email with information about our products which are similar to those which were the subject of a
previous sale to you.
When you access Our Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website.
These server logs may browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify
your browser.
When you send email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries,
respond to your requests and improve our services. We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other
people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, unless we have your consent
to do so.
Disclosure of your information
If we provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of
processing personal information on our behalf, we information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and
any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures, including adequate data protection principles.
We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of such
information is reasonably necessary to:
                        §§   satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process (including without limitation subpoenas and
                             court orders), or enforceable governmental request;
                        §§   enforce applicable terms of service, including investigation of potential violations thereof;
                        §§   detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues;
                        §§   protect against imminent harm to the rights and property of Telecom Luxembourg Private
                             Operator. its users or the public as required or permitted by law;
                        §§   to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
            Company Confidential – Privacy Policy                    Version 1.0                                 page 2|3

If LUXNETWORK S.A. becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we shall provide
notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who
searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement or used particular product
or site functionality. Such information does not identify you individually.
We comply with valid legal process, such as search warrants, court orders, and subpoenas seeking personal information. We
will notify you of any pending legal process unless we are prohibited from doing so by law. We may share information in order
to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the
physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
Your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before
collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third
party for such purposes. You can exercise your right contacting us using our contact details set out below.
We respect your right to access information held about you. Any access request may be subject to a fee to meet our costs in
providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you
follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept
any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Retention of Your information
We take appropriate measures to ensure that any information collected from you is kept secure and kept for only so long as is
necessary for the purpose for which such information is used.
If any of your personal data change or if you have any questions about how we use data collected which relates to you, please
use the functionality on Our Site to update your data. If you do this your data will be updated immediately.
Alternatively, you may contact us with any changes to your personal data. We normally update your personal data within seven
(7) working days of any new or updated personal data being provided to us, to ensure that the personal data we hold about
you is as accurate and up to date as possible.
Changes to this policy
We reserve the right to change this Policy. Any changes made will be posted here.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@LuxNetwork S.A..com
             Company Confidential – Privacy Policy                     Version 1.0                                 page 3|3
